# LAURA QUIRK

Staten Island, NY

## Info

E-mail:

Laurarquirk@gmail.com

Phone:

718-873-6562

## **Skills**

- User Research
- User Flows
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- Frontend Development

## **Tools**

- Adobe XD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Figma
- MS Office

### Education

CareerFoundry

Certification in UX Design | September 2020 - April 2021

Ten month UX Design program.

## **Binghamton University**

Bachelor of Arts in Mathematical Sciences, Minor in Graphic Design | August 2016 - May 2020

# **Professional Summary**

UX Designer with work experience in finance and customer service. Experienced in conducting research to better understand the needs and goals of customers and users. With an education in graphic design, possesses extreme attention to detail. Having earned a Bachelor's degree in mathematical science, specializes in problem solving and analytics.

# **Work History**

## Manager, Waitress

Egger's Ice Cream Parlor | July 2015 - Present

- -Manages a team of employees by delegating tasks and training new hires.
- -Provides the perfect experience for every guest by taking orders and resolving issues.
- -Worked on designing interior layouts for events.

## **Community Assistant**

Chenango Place | March 2019 - June 2020

- -Organizes community events.
- -Responsible for the mail and packages of residents.
- -Liaison between residents and managers.

#### Intern

Cetera Financial Group | June 2019 - August 2019

- -Acquired the necessary skills to become a financial advisor.
- -Attended weekly staff meetings
- -Analyzed a mock client's financial situation with fellow interns and presented our findings as a team to upper management.